Their demand to use Lu Quang for trade must be a part of Chen Zhen's trap.
Only two people can go in.
You and...
Zhao Ling.
Right.
I'm in.
Slow down.
Be smart.
We'll think of another way.
There's no time to argue.
Let's go.
Plan on the drive.
She could be another set of eyes for us.
You're very brave to help.
I've got an idea.
He said I need to be there, but not which one.
What are you getting at?
I'll enter a photo captured by one of the station surveillance cameras.
Then we send that me to the exchange.
We make the trade and wait until Lu Quang is safe.
Then I get out of there.
I'll show up where the photo was taken, and when we're in the clear, I'll rejoin you.
Here.
This is real-time footage of the hall.
I'll be honest.
This plan of yours...
makes no damn sense.
Captain!
Huh?
It worked!
But you were just here and...
Oh, damn.
Not for the easy part.
You ready?
This theater used to be the venue for a lot of magic shows.
These trap doors were put in to accommodate the more elaborate tricks.
Ours will have to be equally as elaborate.
We're dealing with a clever audience.
We won't catch him with this.
I've dealt with him enough to know.
He'll be counting on his ability to let him escape.
He does rely on it heavily.
Almost as if he assumes it's unbeatable.
Plan B, then.
It doesn't matter if he gets away.
Just as long as we know where he is.
I'll hide a tracker in his costume and then disable the metal detector at the door
so they can pass through our security check and be none the wiser.
All right.
Let's see how sneaky you are.
What in the hell?
How did he pull that off?
Huh.
Boss, guess you were right.
He popped up somewhere else just like you said he would.
The police won't wait for long.
They'll rush in as soon as Lu Guang is secured.
We'll need to keep them busy.
And then vanish without a trace.
So then, what to do now?
A grand finale, perhaps?
Something that'll bring the house down.
Ah!
See them?
How close are they to the entrance?